<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<puzzle>
<help>
  <![CDATA[
1. A pretty neat hedgehog lives in a Back Garden, which is divided in four smaller Vegetable fields.
2. Hedgehogs are semi-omnivorous, but this one has a peculiar balanced diet.
3. He eats something different each day, moving CLOCKWISE between vegetables.
4. So, each day, he digs under the garden in a straight line and pops up in next field.
5. He never pops up in the same tile twice (nothing left to eat!)
6. On the last day the Hedgehog needs to be able to correctly reach n.1, closing the trip.  iOS Game: Logic Games/Puzzle Set 1/Hedgehog Orchard  What's up? Cider Party!  Description
1. Having eating a fair amount of vegetables, the Hedgehog switches to fruit and moves to the Orchard.
2. Here a few old apples have become Cider with time!
3. Cider makes the Hedgehog particularly merry, in fact in the Orchard he can move in both directions.
4. Orchard plays like Back Garden, but each move can be Clockwise or Counterclockwise.
5. On the last day the Hedgehog needs to be able to correctly reach n.1, closing the trip.  iOS Game: Logic Games/Puzzle Set 1/Hedgehog Forest  What's up? Lost in the Woods  Description
1. After eating all the fruit, the Hedgehog wanders in the Forest.
2. In the middle, he finds Acorns, which he loves particularly.
3. In order to get Acorns, he can move in and out of the central section (like Orchards).
4. At the margins of the Forest there are a few boulders, with no fruit on them.
5. He can dig under the boulders, but not stop on them (disregard them).
6. The highest number in the Forest is 73. After 73, you don't need to reach n.1, like the Back Garden and Orchard.  Variants
7. He can move in and out the middle section, horizontally or vertically (not diagonally).
8. Numbers go from 1 to 73 and there's no need to loop back to n.1. Boulders can be ignored.  iOS Game: Logic Games/Puzzle Set 1/Hedgehog City  What's up? Mr. Hedgehog goes to Washington  Description
1. In the end, Mr. Hedgehog gets lost in the City after hearing about a 'Big apple'.
2. Having found no such big fruit, he adapts to the City, taking the Tube and eating Junk Food (and Pizza)!
3. The Tube can take Mr. H. across town to the opposite District, in the same exact spot where he was in the starting District.
4. Junk Food has the same effect as Cider on the Hedgehog. Same as in Orchard, he moves Clockwise and Counterclockwise.
5. He also needs to close the trip.  iOS Game: Logic Games/Puzzle Set 1/Hedgehog Enchanted Forest  What's up? Back to Nature!  Description
1. All Forest rules are valid.
2. In addition, the Hedgehog can be magically teleported, just like the Tube in the City.
3. Teleportation happens ONLY in the four quardants (3*3 areas) in the corners.
4. Teleportation takes the Hedgehog to the opposite quadrant, in the same relative position.
5. For example from the South-East quadrant he can be teleported to the North-West one.
  ]]>
</help>
<levels>
  <level id="1">
    <![CDATA[
 30 14  2 31 15   `
 22    18    23   `
    10  6 11  7 27`
 29    17 32 16 28`
        1 36      `
          12 24  4`
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="2">
    <![CDATA[
  1          14   `
 33  9 17    10 34`
 29          22 30`
 32    20    11 31`
 36  8       15 35`
       24    23  3`
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="6">
    <![CDATA[
 22  6            `
                27`
 10 30 34 35 31   `
     5 33    32   `
    29     8      `
 17     1 36      `
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="19" GameType="Orchard">
    <![CDATA[
 32       11 13   `
 36  4 18  1     5`
  8 24 28 27 29  7`
       17  2 30  6`
  9 23 15         `
 33 25 19 26 34   `
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="25" GameType="Forest">
    <![CDATA[
    29    54    46       OO`
 OO          38 72       39`
 OO    63 56  8 64        9`
    28 36 19    33 32 34   `
    70 44    69 13 66      `
     6    55  1    24 48 40`
  3 OO OO 20    12 OO OO 11`
 51          26 50 25      `
    OO    16 68    67 59 15`
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="31" GameType="City">
    <![CDATA[
    23 18 36 15 22`
    33 20 34 31  7`
       26  3 25   `
  1    21 35    17`
 13          32  9`
  5 29 19    30  6`
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="City-3" GameType="City">
    <![CDATA[
  6 24  4  5      `
    12  9 29      `
 27 14 36 31 35  1`
 26     8         `
    13    30 11   `
 32 34  3 33 22  2`
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="City-4" GameType="City">
    <![CDATA[
  9    15       10`
  2        7 18 31`
    23    36      `
 29 22 11    12 30`
    20  5  1     4`
 35 33 26 34    32`
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="City-5" GameType="City">
    <![CDATA[
 35 29 33 34 36   `
 17           3   `
 20 27       11  8`
 31    24 25 30 32`
 21     6     1 15`
    12       10 13`
    ]]>
  </level>
  <level id="Enchanted Forest-1" GameType="Enchanted Forest">
    <![CDATA[
    16 65 28 41       29 67`
 78  6    79 62 74 75 80 36`
 OO 59    50    22    23 51`
 77 58    49 63    48      `
       53 27 61     1      `
     5 72 38 40 21    39   `
       71 70    13 12      `
 76  4 35  3 34     2    33`
    57    26    45 44 25 55`
    ]]>
  </level>
</levels>
</puzzle>
